Rozhkov Dmitrii

Rust software developer

🛘 +7 929 2477436 | @ rozhkovdmitrii@yandex.ru | 🛅 LinkedIn | 🗘 GitHub | 🗣 Yugorsk, Russia

EDUCATION

Ulyanovsk State Technical University

Master degree in Computer Science and Facilities

Ulvanovsk, Russia Sep 2003 - Jun 2010

Profile

I am a more than 12 years experienced back-end developer. I have a background mainly in network and fintech services, blockchain. Currently prefer Rust and C++ but also quite good at python - have several projects written on python. I'm fond of Clean Code, SOLID principles and Design Driven Development. Able to establish processes and manage small team. I'm looking for company of hard-working and well rewarding labor culture. I'm self-organized and outgoing person, always able to find a balance between quality and rushing for the quick result for the company sake.

SKILLS

Computer languages: Rust, C++, Python, pine-script(Trading View), solidity, java-script, action-script, lisp, assembler Tooling:

- Build: cargo, cmake, qmake, GNU make
- Test and Debug: sanitizing, mock-all, google test, google mock, boost test framework, cucumber; wireshark(tshark), netcat, tcpreplay, strace; TDD/BDD
- Queues: kafka
- DB: postgreSQL, clickhouse, prometheus, mysql, firebird, mongodb
- Version control: git, svn, mercurial
- CI/CD: buildkite, GitHub Actions
- Virtualization: vagrant, docker, docker-compose
- Solana: Solana Program Library, Metaplex Program Library, Address Lookup Tables и т.д.
- Ethereum: solidity, truffle, hardhat
- Documentation: Docosaurus, Pelican
- Analytic and logs: Prometheus, Elastic Search (Kebana), Google analytics, Matomo; Vector

Foreign languages: English B2 Upper Intermediate

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

ITPO group

Making My Seven platform that is aimed to provide efficient celebrity and fun base relations.

International, Dubai Dec 2022 - present

- Tokenomica service
- NFT managament service

Rust, Solana Program Library, Metaplex Program Library.

Hana proxy

International, Dubai

L2 Ethterum-compatible middleware based on Sui

- Introducing *Openethereum*'s mempool
- RPC API (jsonrpc)
- CI (GitHub Actions)

Rust, Tokio

Sep 2022 - Nov 2022

Neon labs International, Lisbon Sep 2021 - Sep 2022

L2 Ethterum-compatible middleware based on Solana

- Restructuring design, IPC network layer of Neon Proxy (asyncio, tcp, pickle)
- Logging system (python, asyncio, vector, elastic search, kebana)
- Full test suite (Buildkite)
- Analytics gathering. (Prometheus)
- Documentation. (Docosaurus)

Infatica

International, Singapore

Разработка сетевых сервисов и библиотек, проекты HFT

Aug 2020 - Aug 2021

- Infatica http proxy server: ring buffer based http server (c++, nginx sources, libevent, google mock)
- Infatica SDK: library to be plugged into a desktop app to provide a proxy node (C++, Qt, google mock, google analytics, matomo)
- Infatica Android SDK: aar to be plugged into a Android app to provice a proxy node, reasearch and development. (C++, Qt, JNI)
- Infatica trading-desk: a trading platform, design, management, research on strategies, implementing (python, asyncio, plotly dash, pandas, clickhouse, trading view hooks & pinescript, Finam api)

IskraUralTel

Russia, Yekaterinburg

Lawful interception systems on telephone and ip networks

Jun 2017 - Aug 2020

• Development facilities for: decoding, transcoding, arranging, encrypting, dumping, life-time management, storing statistics and payload of variety protocols and contents accordingly Russian and European laws (stl, boost, libcurl, libcrypt etc.). Testing them (gooble test and mock). Providing testing telecomunication environment (docker, freeradius server, netcat etc.) Making of interprocess communications, based, generally, on ASN1 and Google Protobuf. Making GUI to manage and debug interception in details (Qt).

Gazprom Transgas Yugorsk

Russia, Yugorsk

Corporate management systems

May 2012 - Aug 2017

- Logistic and carrying planning processes automation (1cEnterprise 8.3, javascript).
- Payroll and accounting processes automation (1C Enterprise 7.7)

Simbirsoft FXCM - project Russia, Ulyanovsk

Nov 2010 - May 2012

- Currency management operations transport layer (C++, xslt, libtpt)
 - GUI with Adobe Flex SDK (action script)

Polus-Service LLC.

Russia, Ulyanovsk

e-commerce services and web analytics systems

Oct 2009 - Nov 2010

- Web sites analytic system. Server-side processing, ranging and saving properly analytic packages(c++, qt-network, qt-service, qt-sql и др). Web site analytic agent (JavaScript)
- Household appliances trading processes maintenance system and online-store «Polus» (php, mysql, jquery, pure.js)

Ulyanovsk State Technical University

Russia, Ulyanovsk

Computer center of computer science faculty

Sep 2007 - Okt 2009

- Adopting High performance computer cluster in educational process (Microsoft HPC Pack SDK, Microsoft HPC Server, mpich 1.2.5, c++, MPI, RSA algorithm)
- Cluster Management Panel Web Site (PHP, Microsoft HPC Server)

MY OWN PROJECTS

Python logged groups | GitHub

This package designed to facilitate logging inside classes and functions with @logged group decorator and also makes it possible to manage logging level and any different things for any logging domain mentioned in log cfg.json